{
    "id": "b26ce7f76b084985bfc1788cf76a7ac5",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "‘I can’t swim.’ ‘………………………. can I.’",
            "description": "After a negative statement, we can add another negative statement to it using neither. ",
            "answers": [
                "So",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ………………………….. beautiful.",
            "description": "Too is not possible here it shows negative extremes. ",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We started early so that we ……………………………… there before noon.",
            "description": "When the main clause is in the past tense, might and would are common after so that.",
            "answers": [
                "reach",
                "reached",
                "might reach",
                ""
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I waited for ……………………………. two hours, but he didn’t come.",
            "description": "Another can be used with plural expressions of quantity.",
            "answers": [
                "more",
                "other",
                "another"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Where are …………………………….. students?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "another",
                "other",
                "the other"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I visit my grandparents ………………………….. two weeks.",
            "description": "Every can be used before plural expressions in measurements of frequency.",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "every",
                "each"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you got a lot of ……………………………….?",
            "description": "Luggage does not have a plural form. ",
            "answers": [
                "luggage",
                "luggages"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "My dad and mom …………………………………. me to be a scientist.",
            "description": "When we connect two singular subjects with and, the verb is plural. ",
            "answers": [
                "wants",
                "want",
                "wanting"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The Prime Minister as well as his cabinet ministers ……………………………. to increase spending on defense.",
            "description": "When we connect two nouns with as well as, the verb agrees with the former noun. ",
            "answers": [
                "want",
                "wants"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The woman along with her husband ………………………………… in the lobby.",
            "description": "When we connect two nouns with along with, the verb agrees with the former. ",
            "answers": [
                "is waiting",
                "are waiting"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You and I ……………………………… good friends.",
            "description": "When we connect two pronouns with and, the verb should be plural. ",
            "answers": [
                "am",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It is time you ............................... a job.",
            "description": "Use a simple past after it is time. ",
            "answers": [
                "find",
                "have found",
                "found"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}